JESSICA DEL ROSARIO

204.894.1438 / jessicalimdr@gmail.com / www.linkedin.com/in/jessicalimdelrosario / https://jessicadr.github.io/

PROFILE

I strive to create effective yet attractive design solutions for problems that will improve lives. With a passion for design across all mediums and an academic background in behavioural neuroscience, I found the perfect integration of my skills in UX research/design.

EXPERIENCE

UBC Launch Pad - UX/UI Designer

Vancouver, BC

September 2019 - Current

- UBC Launch Pad is a student-run software engineering team devoted to building software projects in a collaborative, professional environment
- Collaboratively conducting user research, creating wireframes, prototyping, user testing, and branding
- Effectively communicating with a team of developers, business strategists, and designers, while iterating upon feedback

Sprouts @ nwHacks - UX/UI Designer

Vancouver, BC

January 2020

- Within 24 hours, designed and conducted user research for an iOS app that helps users take care of their plants and reduce stress level
- Created high-fidelity designs, interactive prototypes and conducted user tests to validate designs
- Collaborated with a team of developers and created a high-quality product presentation despite the time constraint

Blue Pocket @ BizHacks - UI Designer

Vancouver, BC

January 2020

- Within 24 hours, designed an Android mobile app extension with a team of developers to integrate Best Buy's in-store 'Blue Shirt' service quality with their online shopping platform
- Created user flows, personas, high-fidelity designs, and a product presentation to communicate designs effectively

UBC Student Communications Services - UX Researcher Vancouver, BC

April 2019 - September 2019

- Used mixed user tests and interviews to identify issues and create solutions for users interacting with UBC online platforms
- Produced full case studies, research presentations, and analyzed user data
- Reported to designers for future improvements and changes

SKILLS

Design and Research

Prototyping
Sketching and Storyboarding
User Interviews
Contextual Inquiry
Persona and Scenario Development
Usability Testing
Data analysis
Wireframing

Technical

HTML/CSS, Sketch, InVision, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Adobe Premiere, JavaScript, Procreate

EDUCATION

University of British Columbia

Vancouver, BC September 2017 - Current

- Bachelor of Science, Behavioural Neuroscience

AWARDS

Third Place - BizHacks 2020

- Created Blue Pocket, an Android app extension, with a team of developers, ranking Third Place out of 100+ teams

Emergent BioSolutions Award

Global Specialty Life Sciences Company 2017

 Outstanding academic performance in sciences and commitment to the local community